Bunny Drop
I dunno about tomorrow
It's different than a sacrifice Something's off
I don't think it's like some penalty game
So, why? I don't get it at all
I'm a little bit unsatisfied, but your presence
right now is more than just important
There's no such thing in this world
as something never-ending
Crying isn't painful, it's love's sweet drops, sweet drops!
I want to keep dreaming forever, ya know?
I want to be more kind, ya know?
As long as I'm with you, I'm happy
Girls sure are strong, ya know?
But sometimes we're weak, ya know?
Our wish is to be happy, happy, happy!
And those days will be happy, too!
Just wanna make you happy!
Ms. Saionji...
Go get some sleep.
I'm fine...
In fact, if I fall asleep now, I'll never finish this.
Hey.
Let's get a breath of fresh air.
We're taking a break.
Okay.
See you later.
You guys should take a break when you get the chance as well.
Call my cell if you need anything.
We should have just enough time.
Let's go.
Daikichi!
It's hot...
You're like ice.
You must have been freezing.
Well if I turn off the AC, the boys will sweat on the manuscript.
The cool air helps with stress too.
Oh yeah?
About that new offer you were talking about the other day...
I don't think it's worth it if your current work's quality will drop.
Ma, your body probably won't be able to handle it.
Besides, you're making a decent living as is.
There's no need to be greedy.
But...
What?
I may be popular now, but who knows what the future holds.
There are always new, younger artists appearing.
I could be dropped just like that.
Ma, you worry too much.
It's unhealthy.
You have ink on your face again.
Oh yeah?
Tch...
Ma, you're a girl, so...
I'm not a girl!
I'm a comic artist!
I'm going back to work!
I'm sorry for making a scene...
Jeez...
Going to work is such a pain in the ass.
Good morning...
Morning...
I called you earlier.
Sorry. It was just so hot...
Does that cool you off?
Yeah.
Wanna make your lunch?
Yeah!
Hey, you!
Help me!
Okay!
Rin's summer vacation has started.
In the morning, we make her lunch together,
and then Rin goes to a day-care center.
Wanna visit Grandpa's grave next Saturday?
It's almost time for the Bon Festival, and it's your...
What? Don't want to?
The bellflowers haven't bloomed yet...
It looks they need a little more time.
For now, let's buy flowers at a florist.
We can go again when your flowers bloom.
I guess...
Grandpa will be happy to see the bellflowers you grew.
Right? That's what I thought!
But what would make Grandpa happiest is if you visited.
That's number one.
Yeah...
I understand.
If Rin weren't here, I probably wouldn't be thinking of Grandpa like this.
Rin! Rin!
Kouki!
If you move, it screws the whole thing up!
Whoopsie!
Why is your hair so fine anyway?
I dunno!
What?
Wait up!
Hey! We're gonna be late!
What's with him?
Daikichi, how many more days?
O-Bon Festival
Ten or so, I guess...
I found one!
A cicada shell!
A shell?
This brings back memories...
I've got a bunch of 'em in here.
Gross!
Cut it out!
We're gonna be late!
Hey!
Watch out for cars!
I've been here lots of times before.
With Grandpa?
Yeah.
I see. You know, I think Grandma's laid to rest here too.
Grandpa's grandma?
No, my grandma.
Um, Grandpa and Grandma's daughter is my mom.
And I'm her son.
Your mother is Grandpa's daughter!
But...
Then that makes me your mother's sister...
Crap! I don't want her to think about this!
Here!
It's right here!
The grave's wet.
That jar...
Masako had it...
Ma...
What the hell? She didn't even bother coming to his funeral!
Rin, I'll be right back.
Wait for me right here.
Just pull up the weeds for me!
Okay!
What should I do?
She comes with another man to visit the grave?
Bark! Bark!
What do you want?! What are you doing here?
I thought you were some freak...
I'm supposed to be visiting a grave.
Emphasis on the "supposed to be"...
I thought you might want to know...
Rin's here, too.
At Grandpa's grave...
Um, I...
Look, Rin's important to me, so honestly, I don't think about you.
Nor do I give a damn about your problems.
Unless Rin asks, I have no intention of ever getting you two together.
I know that...
So then why did you go out of your way to follow me?
Do you want to at least take a peek at Rin?
We're going to clean the grave off, light incense, and go home like usual.
It'll take some time...
Well, Rin's waiting for me.
Do what you want.
We're just gonna go about our business.
Rin... Sorry...
Was I gone long?
Um...
Are you okay?
Um... I had to do something...
Never mind, sorry.
Did you wait long?
Not too long.
Were you lonely?
You're weird!
Why so nervous?
I'm not weird.
Here.
'Kay.
Hold it out there.
Okay.
She's no longer a baby...
Blood ties are an amazing thing.
Yep. She looks just like you, Ma.
From behind...
She's pretty cute.
From this far away...
He's a lot like Souichi...
Thank goodness...
That was a surprise.
Maybe a coincidence like this happened because it's nearly Bon...
She's seven years old today...
I see...
I was surprised about your daughter, of course,
but I thought that man was your ex...
Give me a break.
I don't think that man has a single brain cell in that skull.
Although I can't say what he'll be like given another half a century...
Half... a century?
I guess that man was her boyfriend...
Hey, Daikichi?
Well, it's not my place to say anything.
Daikichi!
But some people...
She sure found herself a sweetheart fast enough...
Daikichi, listen!
Ah, what?!
Can we go to Grandpa's house?
It's near here, isn't it?
But that's not Grandpa's house anymore.
Is somebody living there?
No. No one's living there, but the house is my uncle's...
My mom's older brother's house, so...
The family altar is there, too.
I see...
Fine. I'll ask my uncle if we can just go in the yard.
Really?!
Only the yard!
Okay!
I know the way!
I'm going to try that assignment after all.
Seriously?!
Are you sure about this, Ma?!
I'm alone for the sake of my work.
I have to do more.
You're already working plenty!
You work enough for two people!
It's not enough yet...
I have to work so hard I forget what I had for dinner.
Oh, come on. I always forget what I had for dinner...
If I don't...
If I don't forget everything...
I...
We're almost there!
It's the same as before, huh?
But you've totally changed...
They're gone!
The bellflowers!
The dirt's gone too!
The bellflowers were precious to Grandpa!
I'm sure he didn't mean to remove them.
Uncle knows Grandpa's favorite flower at least.
But they wither when winter comes...
Maybe he didn't know that they put out buds again in the spring.
The rocks, too...
If you don't spread them all over like this,
weeds will spring up and become tough to deal with.
Thankfully, we moved Rin's fragrant olive.
Saved its life.
Good thing we have Grandpa's bellflowers at our house too, right?
Because of that, they're still alive!
Exactly!
Maybe change isn't all bad.
But that grave will always be Grandpa's grave, right?
Yeah!
Rin!
Happy birthday.
It's a chocolate cake!
Ms. Saionji, can you do the final check?
Are you okay?
You really might be in over your head this time...
When you say it like that, my hand stops working, so cut it out!
Go ahead.
I'll finish it, for sure.
A sunny early Sunday afternoon
Let's go somewhere today
It's the same road I'm used to traveling
But I can see it sparkling so bright
With the sun shining down its warmth
And you here by my side...
I'm already high, high, high
I feel like dashing out
Sing, la, la, la
My voice out to forever
I'm already high, high, high
Ride the dancing wind
Sing, la, la, la
My voice springs up
Daikichi, the festival stalls are gonna close!
No, they won't!
Sounds just like Grandpa.
Kouki's here!
What's wrong?
We're supposed to meet up at the shrine, remember?
Mom's taking too long!
You're not wearing a yukata?
I can't jump in that!
Was that awesome or what?
Where's your mom?
She said she'd leave after she was dressed, and to meet at the shrine.
Let's go!
Before the festival stalls close!
Daikichi, watch out for cars!
I know!
Wait! It's hard to run in wooden sandals!
I'll carry you!
Forget it!
You can carry me!